{
    "subject": "resource/Spanish_conquest_of_Chiapas",
    "predicate": "property/1p",
    "object": "78",
    "human_readable": "The Spanish conquest of Chiapas had 78 parts.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9019935131072998,
            "question": "What does the number 78 signify in the context of the Spanish conquest of Chiapas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.793757975101471,
            "question": "How many parts did the Spanish conquest of Chiapas involve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6351788640022278,
            "question": "Was the Spanish conquest of Chiapas a lengthy process?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.55648273229599,
            "question": "What were some of the key events or battles during the Spanish conquest of Chiapas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4897063970565796,
            "question": "Can you compare the Spanish conquest of Chiapas to other conquests of the time period?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48466965556144714,
            "question": "What might have contributed to the division of the Spanish conquest into so many parts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46536025404930115,
            "question": "What lasting effects did the Spanish conquest of Chiapas have on the region?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42033347487449646,
            "question": "How did the Spanish conquest of Chiapas impact the indigenous population?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3640473783016205,
            "question": "Can you describe the potential stages or phases represented by these 78 parts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15441356599330902,
            "question": "How is the number 78 significant in historical contexts?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Spanish conquest of Chiapas had 78 parts.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3546_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the potential stages or phases represented by these 78 parts?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3546_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the Spanish conquest of Chiapas impact the indigenous population?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3546_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What lasting effects did the Spanish conquest of Chiapas have on the region?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3546_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3546_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3546_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3546_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3546_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3546_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3546_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3546_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3546_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3546_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3546_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nThe information provided does not mention the number of parts related to the Spanish conquest of Chiapas. Therefore, we cannot support the statement that it had 78 parts based on the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}